ahaurls.info 2018-09-23

# Privacy Policy

AHAURLS.INFO (active site http://ahaurls.info)  
This page describes our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information when you use our services.  
We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy was created with (TermsFeed)  
We use your personal information to provide and improve the service. By using the service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Except as provided in this Privacy Policy, the terms used in the Privacy Policy have the same meaning as in our Terms and Conditions, accessed at http://ahaurls.info.

**Information Collection and use**

While using our services, we may ask you to provide us with some personal information that may be used to contact or identify you. Such information may include, but is not limited to, names, phone numbers, postal addresses, and other information ("Personal Information").

**Login data**

We collect the information that your browser sends whenever you access our services (& quot; Data Import & quot;). This log data may include information such as the Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser version, service pages you visit, The time and date of your visit, the time spent on these pages, and other statistics.

**Cookies**

Cookies are files with small amounts of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your computer's hard drive.  
We use & quot; Cookie & quot; To gather information. You can instruct your browser to reject all cookies or indicate when a cookie is sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not use certain portions of our Services.

**Service providers**

We may use third party companies and individuals to facilitate our services, to provide the Services on our behalf, to perform services related to the Services or to support Help us in analyzing how our services are used.  
Third parties have access to your personal information only to perform the duties on our behalf and are under no obligation to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

**Protect**

Securing your personal information is very important to us, but keep in mind that no method of transmission over the Internet, or electronic means of storage is 100% safe. While we try to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we can not guarantee its absolute security.

**Links To other pages**

Our service contains links to other sites that are not our activity. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to a third party site. We recommend reviewing the privacy policies of each website you visit.  
We have no control over, and are not responsible for the content, privacy policies or performance of any third party websites or services.

**Security for young children**

Our service does not deal with anyone under the age of 13 (& quot; Children & quot;).  
We do not knowingly collect personal information of children under 13. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your children have provided us with personal information, please Contact us. If we discover that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we will remove that information from our servers immediately.

**Change To Privacy Policy**

We may update our privacy policy from time to time. We will notify you of the changes by posting a new security book on this site.  
You should review the privacy policy periodically for any changes. This privacy policy change is effective when posted on this site.

**Contact us**

If you have any questions about privacy policy, please contact us by email: ahaurls.info@gmail.com
